Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXXI. SYSTEM BOARDS
  - Sub-Series 250-416. System Boards. Pan American World Airways, Inc.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1965 (Box 219, Folder 27)
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1965 (Box 219, Folder 28)
      January-June 1965.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1964 (Box 219, Folder 29)
      November 10, 1964-December 1964.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1964 (Box 219, Folder 30)
      February 8, 1964-November 9, 1964.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1964 (Box 219, Folder 31)
      January 1, 1964-February 7, 1964.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1963 (Box 219, Folder 32)
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1958-1960 (Box 220, Folder 2)
      May 14, 1958-April 1960.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1956-1958 (Box 220, Folder 3)
      December 1956-May 13, 1958.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1956 (Box 220, Folder 4)
      September 1954-November 1956.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1953-1954 (Box 220, Folder 5)
      July 1953-August 1954.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1953 (Box 220, Folder 6)
      September 1951-June 1953.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1951 (Box 220, Folder 7)
      June 1948-August 1951.
    - Pan American World Airways, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1946-1948 (Box 220, Folder 8)
      1946-May 1948.
  - Sub-Series 250-416-1. System Boards: Pan American World Airways, Inc.
    - General Office Area District Board of Adjustment, 1966-1969 (Box 220, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 250-416-2. System Boards: Pan American World Airways, Inc.
    - Miami Area District Board of Adjustment, 1966-1969 (Box 220, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 250-416-3. System Boards: Pan American World Airways, Inc.
    - Houston Area District Board of Adjustment, 1966-1969 (Box 220, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 250-416-4. System Boards: Pan American World Airways, Inc.
    - Los Angeles Area District Board of Adjustment, 1966-1969 (Box 220, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 250-416-5. System Boards: Pan American World Airways, Inc.
    - San Juan Area District Board of Adjustment, 1966-1969 (Box 220, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 250-416-6. System Boards: Pan American World Airways, Inc.
    - Cape Kennedy Area District Board of Adjustment, 1966-1969 (Box 220, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 250-416-7. System Boards: Pan American World Airways, Inc.
    - San Francisco Area District Board of Adjustment, 1966-1969 (Box 220, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 250-416-8. System Boards: Pan American World Airways, Inc.
    - Hawaii Area District Board of Adjustment, 1966-1969 (Box 220, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 250-416-9. System Boards: Pan American World Airways, Inc.
    - Seattle-Northwestern Area District Board of Adjustment, 1966-1969 (Box 220, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 250-416-10. System Boards: Pan American World Airways, Inc.
    - Chicago Area District Board of Adjustment, 1966-1969 (Box 220, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 250-416-11. System Boards: Pan American World Airways, Inc.
    - Jetstream Area District Board of Adjustment, 1966-1969 (Box 220, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 250-416-12. System Boards: Pan American World Airways, Inc.
    - John F. Kennedy Airport Area District Board of Adjustment, 1966-1969 (Box 220, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 250-419. System Boards. Oakland Terminal Railway Company
    - Oakland Terminal Railway Company System Board of Adjustment, 1947 (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 250-420. System Boards. Northeast Airlines, Inc.
    - Northeast Airlines, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1947-1954 (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 250-425. System Boards. Niagara, St. Catharines, and Toronto
    - Niagara, St. Catharines, and Toronto System Board of Adjustment, 1945-1960 (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 250-427. System Boards. Freight Forwarding
    - Freight Forwarding System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1964 (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - Freight Forwarding System Board of Adjustment, 1959-1962 (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - Freight Forwarding System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1958 (Box 221, Folder 6)
      July 1954-58.
    - Freight Forwarding System Board of Adjustment (Subject: James Stark Case), 1954-1955 (Box 221, Folder 7)
    - Freight Forwarding System Board of Adjustment, 1939-1954 (Box 221, Folder 8)
      1939-June 1954.
  - Sub-Series 250-428. System Boards. Canadian Interior Navigation Steamship Lines and Stevedoring Companies
    - Canadian Interior Navigation Steamship Lines and Stevedoring Companies System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1969 (Box 221, Folder 9)
      Dissolved, effective August 31, 1969
    - Canadian Interior Navigation Steamship Lines and Stevedoring Companies System Board of Adjustment, 1938-1962 (Box 221, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 250-431. System Boards. Detroit Stock Yards
    - Detroit Stock Yards System Board of Adjustment, 1951 (Box 221, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 250-432. System Boards. Trans-Atlantic Shipping Companies
    - Trans-Atlantic Shipping Companies System Board of Adjustment, 1935-1945 (Box 221, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 250-433. System Boards. North Atlantic Steamship
    - North Atlantic Steamship System Board of Adjustment, 1938-1943 (Box 221, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 250-434. System Boards. South Atlantic Steamship
    - South Atlantic Steamship System Board of Adjustment, 1938-1943 (Box 221, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 250-436. System Boards. Air Transport Industry
    - Air Transport Industry Board of Adjustment, 1950 (Box 221, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 250-437. System Boards. Northwest Airlines, Inc.
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 221, Folder 16)
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1959 (Box 221, Folder 17)
      May 1954-59.
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1954 (Box 221, Folder 18)
      1948-April 1954.
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1946-1947 (Box 221, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 250-438. System Boards. Pennsylvania-Central Airlines, Inc. (Capital Airlines)
    - Pennsylvania-Central Airlines, Inc. (Capital Airlines) System Board of Adjustment, 1950-1955 (Box 221, Folder 20)
    - Pennsylvania-Central Airlines, Inc. (Capital Airlines) System Board of Adjustment, 1947-1949 (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 250-459. System Boards. High Point, Asheboro, and Southern Railroad
    - High Point, Asheboro, and Southern Railroad System Board of Adjustment, 1959 (Box 222, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 250-465. System Boards. Pullman Company
    - Pullman Company System Board of Adjustment, 1953-1960 (Box 222, Folder 3)
      May 17, 1953-60.
    - Pullman Company System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1953 (Box 222, Folder 4)
      December 1951-May 16, 1953.
    - Pullman Company System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1951 (Box 222, Folder 5)
      1921-November 1951.
  - Sub-Series 250-467. System Boards. Utah Idaho Central
    - Utah Idaho Central System Board of Adjustment, 1945 (Box 222, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 250-473. System Boards. Freight Forwarding Company
    - Freight Forwarding Company System Board of Adjustment, 1934-1938 (Box 222, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 250-477. System Boards. Macon, Dublin, and Savannah Railroad
    - Macon, Dublin, and Savannah Railroad System Board of Adjustment, 1945-1959 (Box 222, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 250-482. System Boards. Cumberland and Pennsylvania Railroad Company
    - Cumberland and Pennsylvania Railroad Company System Board of Adjustment, 1953 (Box 222, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 250-488. System Boards. Western Air Lines
    - Western Air Lines System Board of Adjustment, 1958-1962 (Box 222, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 250-489. System Boards. Chicago and Southern Air Lines
    - Chicago and Southern Air Lines System Board of Adjustment, 1947 (Box 222, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 250-490. System Boards. Mid-Continent Airlines
    - Mid-Continent Airlines System Board of Adjustment, 1947-1957 (Box 222, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 250-497. System Boards. Peoria Union Bus Depot
    - Peoria Union Bus Depot System Board of Adjustment, 1954 (Box 222, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 250-499. System Boards. Bamberger Railroad
    - Bamberger Railroad System Board of Adjustment, 1958 (Box 222, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 250-507. System Boards. Central Railroad Company of Pennsylvania
    - Central Railroad Company of Pennsylvania Board of Adjustment, 1953-1954 (Box 222, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 250-510. System Boards. American Overseas Airlines
    - American Overseas Airlines System Board of Adjustment, 1950 (Box 222, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 250-513. System Boards. Missouri Pacific Transportation Company Bus Depot of Memphis, Tennessee
    - Missouri Pacific Transportation Company Bus Depot of Memphis, Tennessee, System Board of Adjustment, 1947-1959 (Box 222, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 250-517. System Boards. Braniff Airways
    - Braniff Airways System Board of Adjustment, 1965-1969 (Box 222, Folder 18)
    - Braniff Airways System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1951 (Box 222, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 250-537. System Boards. Manufacturers Junction Railway
    - Manufacturers Junction Railway Board of Adjustment, 1949 (Box 222, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 250-552. System Boards. Alabama State Docks Terminal
    - Alabama State Docks Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1950-1959 (Box 222, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 250-586. System Boards. State University Railroad
    - State University Railroad Board of Adjustment, 1959 (Box 222, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 250-594. System Boards. Canadian National Central Region
    - Canadian National Central Region System Board of Adjustment, 1936-1943 (Box 222, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 250-597. System Boards. Gulf Steamship
    - Gulf Steamship Board of Adjustment, 1938-1939 (Box 222, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 250-605. System Boards. Canadian Pacific Express
    - Canadian Pacific Express System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1964 (Box 222, Folder 25)
    - Canadian Pacific Express System Board of Adjustment, 1962 (Box 222, Folder 26)
    - Canadian Pacific Express System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1961 (Box 222, Folder 27)
    - Canadian Pacific Express System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1959 (Box 223, Folder 1)
      August 1957-59.
    - Canadian Pacific Express System Board of Adjustment, 1953-1957 (Box 223, Folder 2)
      1953-July 1957.
  - Sub-Series 250-613. System Boards. Montour
    - Montour System Board of Adjustment, 1948 (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 250-616. System Boards. National Air Terminal Service Company
    - National Air Terminal Service Company System Board of Adjustment, 1948 (Box 223, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 250-626. System Boards. Midland Railway Company of Manitoba
    - Midland Railway Company of Manitoba System Board of Adjustment, 1947 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 250-627. System Boards. Youngstown and Southern
    - Youngstown and Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1948 (Box 223, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 250-631. System Boards. Air Cargo, Inc.
    - Air Cargo, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1954 (Box 223, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 250-639. System Boards. Blue Ridge Railroad
    - Blue Ridge Railroad System Board of Adjustment, 1959 (Box 223, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 250-642. System Boards. Lexington Union Station
    - Lexington Union Station System Board of Adjustment, 1953-1959 (Box 223, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 250-672. System Boards. Benwood and Wheeling Connection Railway
    - Benwood and Wheeling Connection Railway System Board of Adjustment, 1961 (Box 223, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 250-675. System Boards. New Orleans Union Passenger Terminal
    - New Orleans Union Passenger Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1954-1962 (Box 223, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 250-676. System Boards. E.W. Coslett and Sons
    - E.W. Coslett and Sons System Board of Adjustment, 1959 (Box 223, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 250-687. System Boards. Bauxite and Northern Railway Company
    - Bauxite and Northern Railway Company System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1955 (Box 223, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 250-712. System Boards. Richard B. Herman Company
    - Richard B. Herman Company Board of Adjustment, 1958-1960 (Box 223, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 250-767. System Boards. Wheeling Cartage Company, Inc.
    - Wheeling Cartage Company, Inc. System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1966 (Box 223, Folder 15)